Guide to the Yale University Press Records
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Publications Committee meeting agendas and minutes and awards won by Yale Press, 1962-2004; Accession 2006-A-146
  - North American Conference on British Studies:Intellectual Life of British Working Class, 2002 (Box 13, Folder 135)
  - Fifth George Wittenban Memorial Award (Box 13, Folder 136)
  - Lyman H. Butterfield Award -Association for Documentary Editing, 1991 (Box 13, Folder 138)
  - Professional/Scholarly Publishing Excellence -Business and Management:Failure and Forgiveness, 1997 (Box 13, Folder 139)
  - Professional/Scholarly Publishing Excellence -Government and Political Science:Civic Ideals, 1997 (Box 13, Folder 140)
  - Columbia University Bancroft Prize:The Rise of American Air Power, 1987 (Box 14, Folder 141)
  - Columbia University Bancroft Prize:Birth Control in America, 1970 (Box 14, Folder 142)
  - David W. and Beatrice C. Evans Biography Award: Barry Goldwater, 1995 (Box 14, Folder 143)
  - Best Western Nonfiction Historical -Frederic Remington and Turn of the Century America, 1995 (Box 14, Folder 144)
  - R. R. Hawkins Award:3000 Years of Chinese Painting, 1997 (Box 14, Folder 145)
  - ASCAP -Deems Taylor Award:Music of Albar Berg, 1997 (Box 14, Folder 146)
  - Caughey Western History Association:Spanish Frontier in North America, 1993 (Box 14, Folder 147)
  - National Jewish Book Award: Jewish Thought:Freud's Moses, 1992 (Box 14, Folder 148)
  - National Jewish Book Award: Holocaust:Texture of Memory, 1994 (Box 14, Folder 149)
  - Hironi Arisawa Memorial Award:Formation of Science in Japan, 1990 (Box 14, Folder 150)
  - ASCAP -Deems Taylor Special Recognition Award:A Ned Rorem Reader, 2002 (Box 14, Folder 151)
  - ASCAP -Deems Taylor Award:Bruno Walter: A World Elsewhere, 2002 (Box 14, Folder 152)
  - ASCAP -Deems Taylor Award:Stravinsky and Balanchine, 2003 (Box 14, Folder 153)
  - American Medical Writers Association:Environmental Cancer: A Political Disease?, 1999 (Box 14, Folder 154)
  - ASCAP -Deems Taylor Award:Thematic Catalogue of the Works of Carl Phillip Emmanuel Bach, 1990 (Box 15, Folder 155)
  - American Bar Association Certificate of Merit:Social Justice in the Liberal State, 1981 (Box 15, Folder 156)
  - Scribes Book Award Honorable Mention:Bill of Rights, 1999 (Box 15, Folder 157)
  - ASCAP -Deems Taylor Award:Musical Form and Transformation, 1994 (Box 15, Folder 158)
  - Citation for Excellence in International Architecture Book Publishing:Roofed Theaters of Classical Antiquity, 1993 (Box 15, Folder 159)
  - Merle Curti Award:Thank you, St. Jude, 1998 (Box 15, Folder 160)
  - ASCAP -Deems Taylor Award:Art of Strict Musical Composition, 1983 (Box 15, Folder 161)
  - ASCAP -Deems Taylor Award:A New Orpheus, 1987 (Box 15, Folder 162)
  - ASCAP -Deems Taylor Award:Leonardo Da Vinci as Musician, 1983 (Box 15, Folder 163)
  - Professional/Scholarly Publishing Excellence:Paris: An Architectural History, 1993 (Box 15, Folder 164)
  - Professional/Scholarly Publishing Excellence:Philosophy and Religion, 1993 (Box 15, Folder 165)
- Publications Committee meeting minutes and background material, 1982-1997; Accession 2011-A-008
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2033.
  - 1982 September 13 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - 1982 October 18 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - 1982 December 13 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - 1983 January 17 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - 1983 February 14 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - 1983 March 14 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - 1983 April 18 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - 1984 December 17 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - 1985 January 14 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - 1985 February 11 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - 1985 March 11 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - 1985 April 15 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - 1985 May 13 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - 1985 June 24 (Box 2, Folder 14-15)
  - 1985 September 16 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - 1985 October 14 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - 1985 November 18 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - 1985 December 16 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - 1986 January 13 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - 1986 February 10 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - 1986 March 17 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - 1986 April 14 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - 1986 May 12 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - 1986 June 23 (Box 3, Folder 25-26)
  - 1986 September 15 (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - 1986 October 20 (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - 1986 November 17 (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - 1986 December 15 (Box 4, Folder 30)
  - 1987 January 19 (Box 4, Folder 31)
  - 1987 February 16 (Box 4, Folder 32)
  - 1987 March 16 (Box 4, Folder 33)
  - 1987 April 20 (Box 4, Folder 34)
  - 1987 May 26 (Box 4, Folder 35)
  - 1987 June 22 (Box 4, Folder 36)
  - 1987 Summer (Box 4, Folder 37)
  - 1987 September 21 (Box 5, Folder 38-39)
  - 1987 October 19 (Box 5, Folder 40)
  - 1987 November 16 (Box 5, Folder 41)
  - 1987 December 14 (Box 5, Folder 42)
  - 1988 January 18 (Box 5, Folder 43)
  - 1988 February 22 (Box 5, Folder 44)
  - 1988 March 21 (Box 5, Folder 45)
  - 1988 April 18 (Box 5, Folder 46)
  - 1988 May 16 (Box 5, Folder 47)
  - 1988 June 20 (Box 6, Folder 48)
  - 1988 Summer (Box 6, Folder 49)
  - 1988 September 19 (Box 6, Folder 50)
  - 1988 October 17 (Box 6, Folder 51)
  - 1988 November 21 (Box 6, Folder 52)
  - 1988 December 19 (Box 6, Folder 53)
  - 1989 January 17 (Box 6, Folder 54)
  - 1989 February 21 (Box 6, Folder 55)
  - 1989 March 20 (Box 6, Folder 56)
  - 1989 April 17 (Box 6, Folder 57)
  - 1989 May 15 (Box 6A, Folder 58)
  - 1989 June 19 (Box 6A, Folder 59-60)
  - 1989 Summer (Box 6A, Folder 61)
  - 1989 September 19 (Box 7, Folder 62)
  - 1989 October 16 (Box 7, Folder 63)
  - 1989 November 20 (Box 7, Folder 64)
  - 1990 September 17 (Box 7, Folder 65)
  - 1990 October 15 (Box 7, Folder 66)
  - 1990 November 19 (Box 7, Folder 67)
  - 1990 December 17 (Box 7, Folder 68)
  - 1991 January 22 (Box 7, Folder 69)
  - 1991 February 19 (Box 8, Folder 70)
  - 1991 March 18 (Box 8, Folder 71)
  - 1991 April 15 (Box 8, Folder 72)
  - 1991 May 13 (Box 8, Folder 73)
  - 1991 June 17 (Box 8, Folder 74)
  - 1991 August 1 (Box 8, Folder 75)
  - 1991 August 1 (Box 8, Folder 76)
  - 1991 September 16 (Box 8, Folder 77)
  - 1991 October 14 (Box 8, Folder 78)
  - 1991 November 18 (Box 8A, Folder 79)
  - 1991 December 16 (Box 8A, Folder 80)
  - 1992 January 27 (Box 8A, Folder 81)
  - 1992 February 24 (Box 9, Folder 82)
  - 1992 March 1 (Box 9, Folder 83)
  - 1992 April 20 (Box 9, Folder 84)
  - 1992 May 18 (Box 9, Folder 85)
  - 1992 June 15 (Box 9, Folder 86)
  - 1992 July 1 (Box 9, Folder 87)
  - 1992 September 21 (Box 9, Folder 88)
  - 1992 October 19 (Box 9, Folder 89)
  - 1992 November 16 (Box 10, Folder 90)
  - 1992 December 14 (Box 10, Folder 91)
  - 1993 January 25 (Box 10, Folder 92)
  - 1993 February 22 (Box 10, Folder 93)
  - 1993 March 22 (Box 10, Folder 94)
  - 1993 April 19 (Box 10, Folder 95)
  - 1993 May 25 (Box 10, Folder 96)
  - 1993 June 21 (Box 10, Folder 97)
  - 1993 September 20 (Box 11, Folder 98)
  - 1993 October 25 (Box 11, Folder 99)
  - 1993 November 22 (Box 11, Folder 100)
  - 1993 December 20 (Box 11, Folder 101)
  - 1994 January 24 (Box 11, Folder 102)
  - 1994 February 22 (Box 11, Folder 103)
  - 1994 March 28 (Box 11A, Folder 104)
  - 1994 April 25 (Box 11A, Folder 105)
  - 1994 May 24 (Box 12, Folder 106)
  - 1994 June 27 (Box 12, Folder 107-108)
  - 1994 August 1 (Box 12, Folder 109)
  - 1994 September 19 (Box 12, Folder 110)
  - 1994 October 17 (Box 12, Folder 111)
  - 1994 November 21 (Box 12, Folder 112)
  - 1994 December 19 (Box 12, Folder 113)
  - 1995 January 17 (Box 12A, Folder 114)
  - 1995 February 13 (Box 13, Folder 115)
  - 1995 March 20 (Box 13, Folder 116)
  - 1995 April 17 (Box 13, Folder 117)
  - 1995 May 15 (Box 13, Folder 118)
  - 1995 June 12 (Box 13, Folder 119)
  - 1995 September 18 (Box 13, Folder 120)
  - 1995 October 16 (Box 14, Folder 121)
  - 1995 November 20 (Box 14, Folder 122)
  - 1995 December 18 (Box 14, Folder 123)
  - 1996 January 16 (Box 14, Folder 124)
  - 1996 February 12 (Box 14, Folder 125)
  - 1996 March 18 (Box 14A, Folder 126)
  - 1996 April 15 (Box 15, Folder 127)
  - 1996 May 20 (Box 15, Folder 128)
  - 1996 June 17 (Box 15, Folder 129)
  - 1996 July 17 (Box 15, Folder 130)
  - 1996 August 13 (Box 15, Folder 131)
  - 1996 September 16 (Box 15, Folder 132)
  - 1996 October 14 (Box 15, Folder 133)
  - 1996 November 18 (Box 16, Folder 134)
  - 1996 December 16 (Box 16, Folder 135)
  - 1997 January 21 (Box 16, Folder 136)
  - 1997 February 18 (Box 16, Folder 137)
  - 1997 March 17 (Box 16, Folder 138)
  - 1997 April 21 (Box 16, Folder 139)
  - 1997 May 19 (Box 17, Folder 140)
  - 1997 June 18 (Box 17, Folder 141)
  - 1997 July 29 (Box 17, Folder 142)
  - 1997 September 22 (Box 17, Folder 143)
  - 1997 October 13 (Box 17, Folder 144)
  - 1997 November 17 (Box 17, Folder 145)
  - 1997 December 15 (Box 17, Folder 146)
- Records, 1909-2004; 1976-2004; Accession 2013-A-079
  Restricted until January 1, 2039
  - Administration department projects
    - General
      - Administration department budget, 1994-1998 (Box 1, Folder 1)
      - Five-year plan (1999-2003), 1998-1999 (Box 1, Folder 3)
      - Handbook, 1990 and undated (Box 1, Folder 4)
      - Mary Cady Tew prize, 1980-1996 (Box 1, Folder 5)
        The Mary Cady Tew prize was discontinued in 1996.
      - Personnel manuals, Circa 1982-1989 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Bookmarks and Endpapers
      - Correspondence, 1985-1989 (Box 1, Folder 7)
      - Mailing lists and distribution, 1983-2001 (Box 1, Folder 8)
      - Production- Endpapers, 1986-1999 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Contracts
      - Handbook, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 10)
      - Revisions, 1976-1991 (Box 1, Folder 11)
      - Revisions, 1993-1994 (Box 1, Folder 12-12A)
    - Governor's Award
      - General, 1987-1997 (Box 1, Folder 13)
      - Clark, The Japanese Company, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 14)
      - Powell, New Masters: Northern Planters During the Civil War and Reconstruction, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 15)
      - Turner, The Greek Heritage in Victorian Britain, 1983 (Box 1, Folder 16)
      - Young-Bruehl, Hannah Arendt: For Love of the World, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 17)
      - Rosenthal, Constable: The Painter and His Landscape, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 18)
      - Crow, Painters and Public Life in Eighteenth-Century Paris, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 19)
      - Oren, Joining the Club: A History of Jews and Yale, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 20)
      - Winn, John Dryden and His World, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 21)
      - Fredriksen, From Jesus to Christ: The Origins of the New Testament Images of Christ, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 22)
      - Tucker, Monet in the '90s: The Series Paintings, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 23)
      - Cannadine, The Decline and Fall of the British Aristocracy, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 24)
      - Galassi, Corot in Italy: Open-Air Painting and the Classical-Landscape Tradition, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 25)
      - Nesbit, Atget's Seven Albums, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 26)
      - Lieven, The Baltic Revolution: Estonia, Latvia, Lithuania and the Path to Independence, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 27)
    - Project MMX (2010)
      - Acquisitions reports, 1990-1991 (Box 1, Folder 28-29)
      - Computers, 1990-1991 (Box 1, Folder 30)
      - London office, 1990-1991 (Box 1, Folder 31)
      - Financial projections, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 33)
      - Manuscript editorial, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 34)
      - Projection and design, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 35)
      - Publications Committee special meeting, 24 June 1991 (Box 1, Folder 36)
      - Sales/marketing department, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Culture and Civilization of China
    - General
      - Project notes from various editors, 1991-1992 (Box 1, Folder 38)
      - Photographs, Circa 1997 (Box 1, Folder 39)
      - Publicity and marketing materials, 1991-1998 (Box 1, Folder 40)
    - Chinese classics
      - Judith A. Calvert files and correspondence, 1993-1995 (Box 2, Folder 41-41A)
      - Crump volume, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 42)
      - Pankenier volume, 1994-1995 (Box 2, Folder 42A)
      - Draft contract, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 43)
      - Otto Bohlmann files and correspondence, 1996-2002 (Box 2, Folder 44-45A)
      - Harbsmeier volume, 1998-2002 (Box 2, Folder 46)
    - Correspondence-Ryden, John G.
      - 1990-1992 (Box 2, Folder 47)
      - 1993-1995 (Box 2, Folder 48)
      - 1996-1999 (Box 2, Folder 49)
    - Editorial
      - Correspondence-Peck, Jim
        - General, 1992-1999 (Box 2, Folder 50)
        - Cahill-urban painters book proposal, 1997-1999 (Box 2, Folder 51)
        - Chinese bronze books (Box 2, Folder 52)
      - Project descriptions, Undated (Box 2, Folder 53)
    - Expenses
      - General, 1993-1999 (Box 2, Folder 54)
      - Archaeology, 1992-1996 (Box 2, Folder 55)
      - Calligraphy, 1995-1996 (Box 2, Folder 56)
      - Companion to classical Chinese writings, 1995-1996 (Box 2, Folder 57)
      - Philosophical concepts, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 58)
      - Sculpture, 1994-1995 (Box 2, Folder 59)
      - Textiles and embroideries, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 60)
  - Director's Files
    - Board of Governors
      - Correspondence and memoranda, 1972-2007 (Box 3, Folder 74-76)
    - Correspondence and office files
      - George Parmly Day
        Related Materials
        See also: George Parmly Day papers (MS 174)
        - 1920 (Box 3, Folder 77)
        - 1938-1954 (Box 3, Folder 78)
        - 1940-1959 (Box 3, Folder 79)
      - Edgar S. Furniss, 1957 (Box 3, Folder 80)
        See also: Provost's Office, Yale University, Records (RU 92).
      - Norman V. Donaldson, 1957 (Box 3, Folder 81)
      - Chester Kerr
        - 1955-1960 (Box 3, Folder 82)
        - 1958-1999 (Box 3, Folder 83)
        - 1963-1964 (Box 3, Folder 84)
        - 1967 (Box 3, Folder 85)
      - John G. Ryden
        - Correspondence
          - 1980-1988 (Box 3, Folder 86)
          - 1989 January-1989 June (Box 3, Folder 87)
          - 1989 July-1989 December (Box 3, Folder 88)
          - 1990 (Box 3, Folder 89)
          - 1991 (Box 4, Folder 90)
          - 1992 (Box 3, Folder 91)
          - 1993 (Box 3, Folder 92)
          - 1994 (Box 3, Folder 93)
          - 1995 (Box 4, Folder 94)
          - 1996 (Box 4, Folder 95)
          - 1997 (Box 4, Folder 96)
          - 1998 (Box 4, Folder 97)
          - 1999-2002 (Box 4, Folder 98)
        - Editorial files
          - Yale Journal of Criticism, 1988-1989 (Box 4, Folder 99)
          - Yale Review, 1988-1994 (Box 4, Folder 100)
          - Human Rights Watch publishing program, 1989-1995 (Box 4, Folder 101)
          - Journal of Law, Economics and Organization, 1989-1991 (Box 4, Folder 102)
          - Yale Shakespeare, 1993 (Box 4, Folder 103)
          - Yale Tercentenary books, 1994-1995 (Box 4, Folder 104)
          - Celebration of John G. Ryden's 23 years at Yale University Press, 2003 (Box 4, Folder 105)
        - Office files
          - John G. Ryden biographical materials, 1978-1992 (Box 4, Folder 106)
          - Local 34 negotiations and strike, 1983 (Box 4, Folder 107)
          - Local 34 negotiations, 1987-1988 (Box 4, Folder 108)
          - Association of American Publishers-Freedom to Read Committee, 1988-1993 (Box 4, Folder 109)
          - Association of American University Presses, 1988-1990 (Box 4, Folder 110)
          - Managerial and Professional union, 1989 (Box 4, Folder 111)
          - Speech before the Class of 1929, 1989 (Box 4, Folder 112)
          - Association of American Publishers, 1990 (Box 4, Folder 113)
          - Speech before Ivy Magazine editors, 1993 (Box 4, Folder 114)
          - Retreats with Executive Team, 1994-2000 (Box 4, Folder 115)
          - Local 34 slow-down, 1996 February (Box 4, Folder 116)
          - Speech at New Haven Public Library, 1996 (Box 4, Folder 117)
          - Speech at Yale Club, re: Culture and Civilization of China project, 1997 (Box 4, Folder 118)
          - Speeches at Sterling Memorial Library, 1998-1999 (Box 4, Folder 119)
          - Beacon Press board, 1998-1999 (Box 4, Folder 120)
          - Tim Rix consulting assignment, 1998-2000 (Box 4, Folder 121)
          - Speech at North End Club, 2001 (Box 4, Folder 122)
          - Introduction of Jaroslav Pelikan, 2003 (Box 4, Folder 123)
    - Operations Committee Meeting Minutes
      Arrangement
      Arranged by fiscal year
      - 1979-1980 (Box 4, Folder 124)
      - 1980-1981 (Box 4, Folder 125)
      - 1981-1982 (Box 4, Folder 126)
      - 1982-1983 (Box 4, Folder 127)
      - 1983-1984 (Box 4, Folder 128)
      - 1984-1985 (Box 4, Folder 129)
      - 1985-1986 (Box 4, Folder 130)
      - 1986-1987 (Box 4, Folder 131)
      - 1987-1988 (Box 4, Folder 132)
      - 1988-1989 (Box 4, Folder 133)
      - 1989-1990 (Box 4, Folder 134)
      - 1990-1991 (Box 4, Folder 135)
    - Publications Committee files
      - Correspondence, memoranda, ephemera and photographs, 1960-2001 (Box 4, Folder 136)
      - Chair of Publications records, 1976-2003 (Box 4, Folder 137)
  - Ephemera (Box 8, Folder 137a)
    3 x 5 American flag given to the Yale University Press for hosting the 1976 annual meeting of the Association of American University Presses. Flag contains the words "AAUP" in blue field where the stars are normally present.
  - Evan's Wing files
    - Alternatives to new wing, 1991 (Box 4, Folder 138)
    - Construction
      - Materials by and about architect, contractors and Yale Facilities, 1989-1992 (Box 4, Folder 139-143)
        Includes John G. Ryden correspondence
      - Contracts with architects, 1990-1991 (Box 4, Folder 144)
      - New Haven Board of Zoning appeals, 1990-1992 (Box 4, Folder 145)
      - Photographs-construction of new wing and renovation of old wing, 1992-1993 (Box 4, Folder 145a)
      - Building signage, 1993-1994 (Box 4, Folder 146)
    - Correspondence and memoranda about Evans Wing
      - 1986 (Box 4, Folder 147)
      - 1989 (Box 4, Folder 148)
      - 1990 January-August (Box 5, Folder 149)
      - 1990 September-December (Box 5, Folder 150)
        Includes records of the Guinzburg reception-October 25, 1990
      - 1991 January-February (Box 5, Folder 151)
      - 1991 March-December (Box 5, Folder 152)
        Includes photographs of Evans gift reception
      - 1992 (Box 5, Folder 153)
        Includes photographs of groundbreaking ceremony
      - 1993 (Box 5, Folder 154-155)
        Includes photographs of Evans Wing dedication
      - 1994-1995 (Box 5, Folder 156)
  - Friends of Yale University Press
    - Events
      - Pelikan talk and reception, 1992 September 10 (Box 5, Folder 163)
      - Robinson, "Thoughts on the Art Book" and keepsake, 1994 May 10 (Box 5, Folder 164)
      - Klehr, "Secret World of American Communism" talk and reception, 1995 May 9 (Box 5, Folder 165)
      - Laqueur, "Holocaust Encyclopedia" reception, 1997 June (Box 5, Folder 166)
      - Class of 1953 reception, 1998 June (Box 5, Folder 167)
      - Miller, "On Reflection" dinner, 1998 October (Box 5, Folder 168)
      - Kernan, "In Plato's Cave" and Klehr, "Venona" events, 1999 May (Box 5, Folder 169)
      - Yale Reunion Week promotion, 2001 May (Box 5, Folder 170)
      - Annals of Communism event, 2001 (Box 5, Folder 171)
    - Membership files
      - Undated (Box 5, Folder 172)
      - 1991 (Box 5, Folder 173)
      - 1992 (Box 5, Folder 174)
      - 1993 (Box 5, Folder 175)
      - 1994 (Box 5, Folder 176)
      - 1995 (Box 5, Folder 177)
      - 1996 (Box 5, Folder 178)
      - 1997 (Box 6, Folder 179)
      - 1998 (Box 6, Folder 180)
      - 1999 (Box 6, Folder 181)
      - 2000 (Box 6, Folder 182-183)
      - 2001 (Box 6, Folder 184)
      - 2002-2003 (Box 6, Folder 185)
      - 2004-2011 (Box 6, Folder 186)
    - Membership lists, 1992-2009 (Box 6, Folder 187)
    - Memoranda and correspondence, 1990-2005 (Box 6, Folder 188-189)
    - Mission statement and history of the program, Circa 1991-1998 (Box 6, Folder 190)
    - Solicitation and marketing materials, 1992-2003 (Box 6, Folder 191)
    - Special dedication page, 2001 (Box 6, Folder 192)
    - Yale University Press web site, 2002-2004 (Box 6, Folder 193)
  - Historical files
    - General
      - Association of American University Presses annual meeting, 1976 (Box 6, Folder 193A)
      - Histories of the Yale University Press, 1914-1997 (Box 6, Folder 194)
      - Press clippings, 1921-1960 (Box 6, Folder 195)
    - Anniversary files
      - Fiftieth anniversary, 1958 (Box 6, Folder 196)
      - Seventy-Fifth anniversary, 1983 (Box 6, Folder 197)
      - Exhibit for Yale Tercentennial (Box 6, Folder 198)
    - Departments
      - Administration-records of the Assistant to the Director, 1986-1989 (Box 6, Folder 198A)
      - Acquisitions
        - Procedures and guidelines, 1979-1994 (Box 6, Folder 199)
        - Reference publishing program, 1990-1991 (Box 6, Folder 201)
      - Design and Production
        - Book jackets, 1956-1963 (Box 6, Folder 202)
        - Production and guidelines, 1991 (Box 6, Folder 203)
      - Manuscript Editorial-procedures and guidelines, 1982-1999 (Box 6, Folder 204)
      - Marketing
        - Catalogs and brochures, Undated (Box 6, Folder 205)
        - Advertising, 1958-2000 (Box 6, Folder 206)
        - Publicity, 1991-1999 (Box 6, Folder 207)
        - Information Media Guaranty Program (IMGP), 1963-1966 (Box 7, Folder 208-210)
      - Yale Printing Service, 1964 and Undated (Box 7, Folder 211)
    - E-Publishing
      - General files, 1985-2001 (Box 7, Folder 212)
      - In-house database, 1997-2004 (Box 7, Folder 213)
      - Initiatives, 2001-2004 (Box 7, Folder 214)
    - Homes of the Yale University Press
      - General, 1958-1972 (Box 7, Folder 215)
      - 149 York Street, Undated (Box 7, Folder 216)
      - Branford, CT warehouse, Undated (Box 7, Folder 217)
      - 143 Elm Street, 1958-1959 (Box 7, Folder 218)
      - 302 Temple Street, 1973 (Box 7, Folder 219)
    - Publishing projects
      - Reference books proposals, 1968-1995 (Box 7, Folder 220)
      - Regional publishing program proposal, 1988-1989 (Box 7, Folder 221)
      - Transformation of American Democracy series, 1998-1999 (Box 7, Folder 222)
      - Yale Law School publishing program, 1998 (Box 7, Folder 223)
    - Staff
      - Memoranda, 1979-2002 (Box 7, Folder 224)
      - Photographs, 1954-1998 (Box 7, Folder 225-226)
      - Personnel files, 1979-1999 (Box 7, Folder 227)
        Folder restricted until January 1, 2074
      - Edward Tripp memorial, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 228)
  - London office
    - Association of Scientific, Technical and Managerial Staffs (ASTMS), 1973-1981 (Box 7, Folder 229-230)
    - Audit reports, 1984-1991 (Box 7, Folder 231)
    - Correspondence
      - 1975 (Box 7, Folder 234)
      - 1976 (Box 7, Folder 235)
      - 1977 (Box 7, Folder 236)
      - 1978 (Box 7, Folder 237)
      - 1979 (Box 7, Folder 238)
      - 1979-2002 (Box 7, Folder 239-240)
    - Financial statements
      - 1981-1994 (Box 7, Folder 241)
      - 1995-1999 (Box 7, Folder 242-243)
    - Location files
      - Summaries, 1961-1981 (Box 7, Folder 244)
      - 20 Bloomsbury Square, 1973 (Box 9, Folder 245)
      - 13 Bedford Square, 1980-1988 (Box 9, Folder 246)
      - 23 Pond Street, 1988-1990 (Box 9, Folder 247)
    - Management accounts
      - 1979-1987 (Box 9, Folder 248)
      - 1990-2003 (Box 9, Folder 249)
      - Sales/operating forecasts, 1975-1988 (Box 9, Folder 250-251)
    - Melon Centre, 1975-1984 (Box 9, Folder 252)
    - Nicoll, John files, 1978-1988 (Box 9, Folder 253)
    - Pension plan, 1985-2003 (Box 9, Folder 254)
    - Purchase of Ken Dickson Marketing, Ltd, 1991 (Box 9, Folder 255)
  - Manufacturing and Sales Ledger, Circa 1909-1920 (Box 16, Folder 255a)
  - Publication Committee meeting files
    - 1976 February 9 (Box 9, Folder 256)
    - 1976 March 29 (Box 9, Folder 257)
    - 1976 April 19 (Box 9, Folder 258)
    - 1976 May 10 (Box 9, Folder 259)
    - 1976 June 14 (Box 9, Folder 260)
    - 1976 September 13 (Box 9, Folder 261)
    - 1976 October 25 (Box 9, Folder 262)
    - 1976 November 15 (Box 9, Folder 263)